Scientist ₹2 Please like, share and
subscribe Like a group
collapsed ICICI Lombard's work with water 6
Yesterday there was a conversation with a high security
number
weak but it was
saying that in stock and it was
actually doing 1300 in 1617
Management commentary now see thousands of people
share about themselves whatever you
do from here it will take
some more quotes
for this porn it is just mute
and is
known as this and the
problem is definitely quizzical that he
said that he had the highest impact on Africa, it will
not have any impact in the police physical quarters so it will definitely be seen helping one
but half sir you will
keep its chart Agarwal please call on Kumar
that you people
who is his award at this time as you
said that entry through many means can be
seen in the coming days and the
way it is busy that LIC
's tube can be very high so in a way the
insurance papers held
are in Lombard General Insurance, not in Life
but my own  I believe that if there is a
glut of insurance papers
in the market, then the back will be troubled from there. So
I think that at this time, we should do a little world
and tighten it a little. If the next
quarterly results are better, then it can be seen there. At this
time, if someone wants to take a
position in insurance, then I
think SBI Life
could be a better option,
a stylized, better option.
Even in the morning, when fundamental issues were raised, Maheshwari had
spent time with ICICI Lombard. At
this time, he also wanted to allocate space
including a plot. But if you
still want to bet on it, then
SBI Life seems to be a better police end.
Now tell me brother, instead of shallowing it, as per the way
we have seen that
in this, two sons are licking
each other and 2222, both are
preparing to subscribe, so
I can cut from here to subscribe.
What happened in it, such looting view and you
people have
sent an extraordinary death in detail of this one bank,
whose numbers are to be known tomorrow.